Seward, Ralph T. Papers 5328
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: Arbitration Cases, Railroad
  - 'Before the Arbitration Board' Folder 6, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Reports of the Presidential Railroad Commission, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - CX6, CX52, CX80, CX81, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - CX51, CRX-16A, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Before the Arbitration Board Folder 1, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Before the Arbitration Board Folder 2, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Before the Arbitration Board Folder 3, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Before the Arbitration Board Folder 4, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Before the Arbitration Board Folder 5, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Carriers' Rebuttal Submission No. 8, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Scope and Contents
    Several Photographs
  - BRT vs. CHI, Mil., St. Paul [USDC,DC] & Pac R.R. Co. and Ralph T. Seward - Civil No. 2634-65 and No. 3227-65 and Misc., 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Bro. of Loco. Fireman & Engineers, et al v. C. B. & Q. et al and Ralph T. Seward., 1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Before the United States Senate Committee on Commerce - Statements, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Before the United States Senate Committee on Commerce - Hearing, Folder 1, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Before the United States Senate Committee on Commerce - Hearing, Folder 2, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Litigation Files, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - B.L.F.&E vs. C.B.&Q. et al Civil Action No. 2919-63 B.L.E. v. Union Pacific et al Civil Action No. 2921-63 Carriers & BLE Employees Civil Action No. 41-63, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - U.S.C.D., D.C. - Action No. 201-66 BRT vs. St. Louis Southwestern Ry Co. and RALPH T. SEWARD.: Petition to Impeach and Contest Rulings, Arb. Bd. 282. (Q. #47), 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - U.S.C.D.,D.C.--Civ.Act.#1273-64, #1277-64 BRT v. C,B,&; Q. et al. B.L.E. v. Union Pacific RR, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Administration of Public Law 88-108, James E. Wolfe, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Neutral Members filed with Committee 8-31-65 Final Copy as Reproduced and Filed Prepared by R.T.S., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Litigation - Documents, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Commerce - Public Law 88-108 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Hearings on the Administration of Public Law 88-108, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Statement of Ralph T. Seward 8/31/65, Folder 1, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Statement of Ralph T. Seward 8/31/65, Folder 2, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Statement of Ralph T. Seward 8/31/65, Folder 3, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Statement of Ralph T. Seward 8/31/65, Folder 4, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Statement of Ralph T. Seward 8/31/65, Folder 5, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Solicitors Answers re Absent Neutral Arbitrators (Donohue), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Compilation of Interpretations by Arb. Bd. 282 May 17, 1964 thru Oct. 23, 1964 by Natl. Railway Labor Conf. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ralph T. Seward Documents, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Questions Submitted by the Carriers' involving the provisions of Award of Arbitration Board No. 282, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Joint Carrier & BLF&E Question Filed 2/17/66-- Answered 2/20/66 by Board, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - S.U.N.A.: Correspondence and Questions, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Switchmen's Union Folder 1, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Switchmen's Union Folder 2 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - B.L.E.:- Correspondence and Questions, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration Board No. 282 Board, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - B.R.T.: Correspondence and Questions, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder 1, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder 2, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen vs. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul Pac. Railroad Lines, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Chi. Mil. St. Paul Pacific Railroad Co. and B.R.T. Folder 1, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Chi. Mil. St. Paul Pacific Railroad Co. and B.R.T. Folder 2, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder 2, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #3, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Appendices to the Response by the Carriers to B.R.T. Question No. 36, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #4, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #6, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #7, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #8, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #9, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Folder #10, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - B.R.T. Question No. 36, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - B.R.T. Question No. 36 Folder 2, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Statement of Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen regarding Controversies, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Civil Action No. 1641-64, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - B.L.F. & E.---Correspondence & Questions, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - O.R.C. & B. Correspondence & Questions, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - B.L.F.&E. and B.R.T. Joint Question submitted 11/3/65:Answered 1-16-66, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Board No. 282, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Board 'Use of Firemen on other than Steam Power Consist of Road and Yard Crews', 1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Employee Exhibits, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Before the Senate Commerce Committee (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Reference Book Award of Arbitration Board 282, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - B.L.F.E., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Experience in Yard Service and Freight with and without the Employment of Firemen, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - B.L.F.E. vs Denver and Rio Western Railroad Company, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Book, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Board No. 282, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - B.L.F.E., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Hearings on the Administration of Public Law No. 88-108, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Board Dispute Volume No. 10, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration Board Dispute Volume No. 14, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Board Dispute Volume No. 11, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Board Dispute Volume No. 12, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Report of the Presidential Railroad Commission, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Work Rules Dispute, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Work Rules Dispute, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Before the Arbitration Board, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - B.L.E. court readings, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Thaddeus Krol Fatality, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Employees' Exhibits, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Employees' Exhibits and Rebuttals, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Requirements, Skills, Responsibilities and Duties of Trainmen And Yardmen, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen of North America, 1945-1950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Colombia Typographical Union Agreements, 1944-1955 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - International Association of Machinists, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers Local 104 & Local 156, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - UAW-CIO Agreements, 1948-1961 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Agreements, 1945-1955 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Manuals, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America CIO Agreements, 1945-1952 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - United Steelworkers of America Agreements Folder 1, 1942-1956 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - United Steelworkers of America Agreements Folder 2, 1947-1956 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - United Steelworkers of America Agreements Folder 3, 1947-1956 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - GMC - Delco Products Div. - Local 755 Case E-571 and F-57 - Umpire Dec F-47, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - GMC - Delco Products Div. - Local 755 Case E-517 and E-552 - Umpire Dec. E-115, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - E-517 & E-552, E-115 Delco, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - E-57 Delco E-114, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - E-571 & F-57 Delco F-47, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Series IV: Arbitration Cases, General Motors
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Case No. E-534 E-104, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - GMC - Delco Products Div. - Local 755 Case E-57 - Umpire Decision E-114, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Case No. E-545, E-103, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - GMC - Delco Products Case No. E-615, E-102, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Case E-485, E-101, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Case No. E-502 E-100, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Case No. E-521 & E-441, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Case No. E-476, E-98, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-195 Umpire Decision No. E_46, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Local 755 - Case No. E-202 & E-204 Umpire Decision No. E-45, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. D-396 Umpire Decision No. D-121, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division Local 755 - Case No. F-1 Decision No. F-1, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-232 & E-48 Umpire Decision No. E-44, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-83 - Umpire Decision No. E-43, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-60 and E-67 Umpire Decision No. E-42, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-75 Umpire Decision No. E-41, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-574 Decision No. E-40, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - GMC - Delco Products Division - Local 755 - Case No. E-117 - Decision No. E-39, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - GMC - Delco Appliance Division - Umpire Decision No. E-23, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - GMC - Delco Appliance Division Umpire Decision No. E-22, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - GMC - Delco Appliance Division - Umpire Decision No. E-21, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - GMC - Delco Remy Division - Delco Battery Operations - New Jersey Umpire Decision No. E-20, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - GMC - Delco Appliance Division - Umpire Decision No. E-19, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - GMC - Delco Appliance Division - Umpire Decision No. E-18, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Electro-Motive Decision - GM Special Decision On Case No. 10, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Grievance No. F-982 11/2/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Grievance No. F-991 Dec F-50, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Grievances F-987, 988, 990 11/20/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Grievance No. F-917 11/2/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - General Motors- Frigidaire Case No. F-793 & F-823 Decision No. F-44 11/4/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - General Motors-Frigidaire Case No. F-982 Decision No. F-51 11/2/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case No. F-609 #F-40 7/28/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Umpire Decision # F-61 Grievance No. F-970, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Grievance No. F-472 3/23/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Grievance No. F-956 3/23/53, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Misc., 1953 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Div. - Local 801 Case F-1035 - Umpire Decision F-46 11/3/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - F. 841 Frigidaire F-45, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case No. F-714 F-42, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - F-913 Frigidaire F-43, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 901 - Case No. F-221 F-39 11/3/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case No. F-618 and F-681 11/3/51, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801 - Case NO. F-465 Umpire Decision No. F-34 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case No. F-486 Umpire Decision No. F-33 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 10/24/52 801 - Case No. F-465 F-34 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case No. F-739, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case No. F-624 F-36 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case NO. F-652 and 651 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801 - Case No. F-459 & F-460 10/6/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801 - Case No. F-433 Umpire Decision No. F-30 9/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case No. F-353 Umpire Decision NO. F-29 9/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local NO. 801 - Case No. F-353 Umpire Decision No. F-29 9/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Umpire Decision, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case NO. F-353 Umpire Decision No. F-28 9/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local NO. 801 - Case No. F-319 Umpire Decision No. F-27 9/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case No. F-445 Umpire Decision No. F-26 9/5/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case F-535 Decision F-24 9/15/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case No. F-251 Umpire Decision No. F-25 9/15/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case Nos. 708 and F-741 F-23 9/15/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case No. F-473 9/15/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case No. F-305 8/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case NO. F-305 Umpire Decision No. F-21 8/29/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801 - Case No. F793 and F823 11/4/52, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Railroad Shopcraft Fact-finding Study, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Reports + Cases, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - American Bridge Company and United Steelworkers of America C.I.O. NO. 1270, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Railroad shop crafts Negotiations 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - National Mediation Board No. 176 Case A - 8563, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - National Mediation Board No. 176 Case A - 8563, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - National Mediation Board No. 176 Case A - 8563, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Before Emergency Board No. 176 Folder 1, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Before Emergency Board No. 176, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Before Emergency Board No. 176, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - New York and New Jersey Milk Dealers, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Wisconsin Steel Company and Progressive Steelworkers Union, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Company Local 1229 - Grievance 1458, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Wisconsin Steel Company and Progressive Steel Workers Union, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Misc., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801, Case Nos. F-1, F-379, 484 Umpire Decision No. F-20, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local No. 801 - Case No. F-98 Umpire Decision No. F-19 8/15/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801 - Case Nos. F-268, 322, 370, 399 and 447. (F-18) 8/15/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Local 801 - Case No. F-78 Umpire Decision No. F-17 8/15/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case No. F-146 8/15/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case No. F-2 8/15/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case NO. E-535, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - GMC - Local 801 - Case No. E-547 8/15/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-96 case No. E-448 1/4/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-95 Case No. E-418 1/4/52, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-97 Case No. E-450 1/4/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division NO. E-93 Case NO. E-411 12/20/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-94 Case No. E-377 1/4/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-92 Case NO. E-346 12/20/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-91 Case NO. E-426, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-90 Case No. E-368 12/20/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Case NO. E-351 12/20/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division E-88 Case NO. E-370 12/20/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Newark Zone Shop - Umpire Decision 3 2/21/50, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Newark Zone Shop - Umpire Decision 2 2/21/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Newark Zone Shop - Umpire Decision 1, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. D-120 11/16/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. 38 11/15/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. E-37 11/15/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Umpire Decision No. E-36 11/14/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. E-30 11/14/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case No. F-486 11/4/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Local 801 - Case NO. F-492 10/22/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. E-31 10/22/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. D-119 10/21/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Umpire Decision NO. E-29 10/21/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. D-118 10/21/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Umpire Decision No. E-28 10/20/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. E-24, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. E-27 10/19/49 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division - Umpire Decision No. E-26 10/14/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - GMC - Frigidaire Division Umpire Decision No. E-25 10/14/49, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - GMC - Inland Mfg. Div. -Case G-20 Local 87-United Cork etc., 1953 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Case No. E-215 5/21/52, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case NO. F-15 Umpire Decision NO. F-4, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Company Local 717 - Case No. F-105 Umpire Decision No. F-3 3/13/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. 259 Umpire Decision No. 72 5/13/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case E-177 & E-205 Umpire Decision No. E-66 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-215 Umpire Decision No. E-65 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case E-101 & E-121 Umpire Decision No. E-64 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-173 & E-174 Umpire Decision No. E-63 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case E-115 & E-118 Umpire Decision No. E-67 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-245 Umpire Decision NO. 68 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-255 Umpire Decision No. 69 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-158 Umpire Decision No. 70 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case NO. F-88 Umpire Decision NO. F-2 3/7/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. 171 3/12/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-212 Umpire Decision No. E-62 3/7/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case No. E-71-B Umpire Decision No. E-61 3/6/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - GMC - Packard Electric Division Local 717 - Case NO. E-23 Umpire Decision NO. E-60 3/6/51, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 55)
- Series V: Chairman's Files
  - Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Board of Conciliation & Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Board of Conciliation & Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Transportation Co. vs. United Steel workers of America, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company vs. Local 3068 United Steelworkers of America, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Grievances 123, 124, 125 and 126, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Fair Days Work Policies & Procedures of June 30, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Fair Day's Work Program - Policies and Procedures, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - System Board of Adjustment, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Columbia-Southern Chemical Corporation and International Chemical Workers Union, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 14)